Hello everyone, good evening everyone
Can everyone hear my voice?
Good evening everyone
Tomorrow is our birthday
Today we are going to talk about our Christmas theme
This time we have provided you with the DXF document
It is the same as the previous way of obtaining
Then we open a model
Or open a model downloaded from Connect
You can download directly from Connect
OK
Then make it a left-to-right symmetry
Then put our symmetry board
It's the same as before
Let's put it up first
Give it a position
Because the gingerbread man is next to me
My board is not easy to put
Then arrange our board to the model
Then we
Then this
Cut off this part
We make a double layer
Do a double layer
We use this shortcut to arrange for her to do a layer relationship
Make a layer relationship first
I delete the other side first
So that I can do a topography right away
Because of making layer relationship like this
I just need to do layer relationship once
Don't do it on the other side
Then it is also arranged directly for him
Then arrange the collar for him
Make it a little bit bigger
Let's put the main body together
We are going to put the gingerbread man, snowflake and Christmas tree together later
We are going to make an opening on the side of the sleeve
We are going to fold it down
We are going to make a backlight on the other side
I made a backlight here
Open the model
Make a little bit of the sleeve
I forgot to sew it, I will make it up later
We are going to make a backlight on the side of the Christmas tree
according to the base line
We will make a simple seam
We put it next to it
Here, the two sleeves are cut together
We make it move together
So that we won't make a mistake when we apply other materials
later
Then we cut this Christmas tree for him
And then there's a Christmas tree on the front
And here because it's a symmetrical one right now we're going to take it out of its joint or we're going to cut it off and we're going to cut it off on the other side
So we're just going to do the simple one and we're just going to cut it
And here we're going to cut it off
If you don't think it's good, you can hide this line so that it's a little bit clearer
Here we are with our Christmas tree
And then we're going to deal with some of the other versions of this one with our
Snowflakes in the middle of the snowflakes we're going to sew them together with this dress and we're going to take these little circles and we're going to hook them up
And then we're going to sew them together
And then we're going to go a little back and then we're going to come to the bottom and we're going to kind of do the front and then this side
And this one here that's not hooked up and then I'm going to take another row
And then
And then we're going to start putting this snowflake on top of our model and put this on top of this dress
Well, let's have a look at this snowflake
There are the big spots
This one is small, and this one is a board
And we are going to put it in the middle first
And then make a copy
Make a copy and paste it
And then put it together with the big circle
It feels like this part is a little dense, so I'm going to put it on the other side
And then we make a arrangement
Just arrange it directly to the outside
Let me show you how it works
This is the big snowflake, and then we make the small one
And then we make the small one
The circle here, you don't have to be the same as me, you can also set the circle and the size of the snowflake freely.
Here seems to be one more.
Just delete the other one.
Then it is also arranged to be added to the outside.
Then the other side is the same.
There is also this circle on the other side.
Do a copy and paste of the same.
The rest are the same.
Do the same as before.
We are going to make a seam for it.
There are a few small circles here.
Let's hook it up.
Hook it up into a sheet.
Then we sew it up.
That's it.
There is not only the top of the item.
There are also several of the socioeconomicíafat.
All of this arrived at the bottom of theCuLin esto is trend so it would be a
bit embarrassing that this is sold.
Only six.
and just sew it
Now we will sew the gingerbread man
and sew the gingerbread man together with the dress
There are also these snowflakes on the sleeves
Don't forget to sew them
Now we will sew the snowflakes together with the sleeves
Don't forget to sew them together with the sleeves
Now we will sew the dress
We will sew the snowflakes together with the sleeves
and make a symmetry on the other side
Now we will sew the circles on the gingerbread man
These circles are for
making a style with the dress
These are just the circles of the dress
Just sew them together
Now we will sew this one
We will sew this one
Then make a seam
Then we will make the bottom layer of this gingerbread man
After we finish the bottom layer, we have to follow it
Because we want to make a double layer effect for it
Then in the middle, let's put these basic lines out for it
Then we make a cologne layer for it
Make a cologne layer from the outside
In this way, the inner line can be automatically sewed together
Then we remove this joint
Because some of the original three big circles we don't need
So we delete it
Then simulate
Then we make the details of the gingerbread man
For example, the details on his hat
I didn't align it here
Let's do it again
Then hook it up as a plate
Then with our
This one
I'm going to make a seam along with our inner line
When sewing on the side here
Pay attention to the bana tau
Change it to patterns
It's the same
Add to it
outside
It's the same
Add it to the outside
然后还有这个它的围巾 And then there's this scarf
我们是直接把它刻龙成了板片 We just cut it into pieces
然后也是添加到外面 Then add it to the outside
然后这个下面有一些圆 Then there are some circles below this
我们给它做一些圆的那种装饰 We make some round decorations for it
直接用这个内部圆给它画 We draw it directly with this inner circle
然后给它做一个复制粘贴就可以了 Then make a copy and paste for it
底下也是一样的 It's the same at the bottom
这个我们给它画五个圆 We draw five circles for it
侧边可以再摆一个 We can put another one on the side
然后可以调整一下位置 Then we can adjust the position
然后我们把这些内部圆给它做一个剪签缝纫 Then we make these inner circles a cut-and-paste
这样子一会儿我们就可以给它做一个撞布的这样一个设计 We can make a cover for it later
围巾上也是一样的 The scarf is the same
给它做一些这种圆圆的装饰 We make some round decorations for it
这里的位置的话可以自由的调整 We can adjust the position here
不一定要跟我一样 It doesn't have to be the same as mine
然后我们也是一样的做剪签缝纫 We also make the same cut-and-paste
好的 We can also make someним的
然后把未完成的小叶子和叶子 All the pieces are finished
然后我们就把它弄成一个圆圆的圆圆的双圆圆 We can use it as a cover
然后它就会用 typing tool
我们可以画一个圆圆的圆圆的圆圆围 Let us draw a picture with our drawing
然后给它彻底的圆圆的圆圆的圆圆 We can draw the shape of the leaf
然后把我们用的这个叶子用这个圆圆的圆圆的圆圆的圆圆 We can draw the shape of the leaf
还有我们可以用一个圆圆的圆圆的圆圆的圆圆的圆圆 We can draw the shape of the leaf
And then this little leaf is also a small decoration on the hat
I'm going to draw a little circle on top of it and then we're going to put it on top of it and that leaf
All right, so we added two three colors
I'm going to use the quick arrangement, which I've arranged on top of it
The arrangement is a little bit closer to each other
When you're modeling like this
he won't
so that there won't be too much shaking.
I'll show you the simulation.
It looks like this.
Put your hand down first.
The gingerbread man is pressed down by his hand.
Let's move the gingerbread man out a little bit.
And then we'll give him some air.
So that the whole thing can swell up.
And then we'll give him all the panels related to the gingerbread man.
Including the round panels for decoration.
They are all to be selected.
Let's move it out.
Move it to the outside of the arm.
Don't press it with your arm.
We'll freeze the other panels.
And then we'll simulate the gingerbread man alone.
And then we'll activate it together.
And then we'll simulate the effect together.
And then we'll apply a fabric to it.
The texture of this fabric.
You can refer to the trade live of the last issue.
Including my Shoukefu.
Let's apply other Loewen fabrics to it.
And then here we'll give him one.
Select this Christmas tree for him.
And then apply a piece of fabric like a big body.
Let's change the color for him.
We can change the color to green.
This way it will be closer to the Christmas tree.
This is the effect.
You can see the effect now.
You'll see something in this shape, but it needs to change up a little bit.
Ah, we put him a piece of cotton again.
Well, here I am using random fabric.
Let's see what.
Here, okay?
That's the end of the learned handmade pattern.
We made these for him.
Remember, you'll not forget the 2 sencillettes.
Don't forget that there are two filaments
All need to be selected
Then give a simulation
In order to make this snowflake version
Can become harder
We give it a sticky layer
We can give it a sticky layer
Then change this preset to a slightly harder one
This kind of sticky layer
We can put this snowflake version
Add it to the outside again
Let it rearrange its position
Then simulate again
You can see it like this
Now this whole version is that kind of
A more three-dimensional state
Not like the soft one just now
Then let's take a look at the gingerbread man
Give him a face of Yang Bao
So that it can become more three-dimensional
Then a little bit more texture
Then I can change it to this kind of
The only yellow face of the gingerbread man
Color
Pay attention to this
We want to make its texture
Give it a bright color first
Otherwise it is a black texture
We can't see any color on it
Let's adjust the color of the whole of this gingerbread man
I just felt that it was a little bit
The color is too dark
It's a little bit too yellow
Then we continue
Let's make this face a copy
Then give it different colors
For example, the hat can be changed to this kind of black
Then continue to copy
This other version
For example, this one on the hat
This is the decorative bag
Change it to red
Then this leaf on this hat
I will replace the leaves on the hat with this kind of green
And this scarf
And these small circles for decoration on the hat and scarf
I can replace it with this kind of white
I will show you how to do it
You can see that there is no mouth on the gingerbread man
Let's draw the mouth
Use the internal multidirectional line function
Connect the two sides
Draw some curve points
And the mouth
Draw a line
And we are going to draw the mouth
Draw the line
And the curve point
then divide it into two
use a piece of black fabric
add two buttons to the eye
to create the eye shape
use a piece of black fabric
add two buttons to the eye
to create the eye shape
the size of the button
can be slightly larger
to cover the inner circle
to give it a plastic glow
then change it to black
add two pieces of blusher
to the button
to give it a plastic glow
to create a pink effect
the size can be slightly larger
then on the hat
we also add a button to cover the circle
and the seam
this one is also a little difficult
to just pull it out
and leave it for a while
put it on the body
too easy
this is trying to go back to it's base
with some more colour
like this
to make it more담per
use leaf
leave it to grow
notice me
to…
let it dry
then use a movie passion
Then we put the other basic lines on Jiang Min Ren's body
Give him a look first
Then we sew a strip on it
We can also add it directly to the outside and then make it a symmetry or copy and paste
Let's make a bump after we're done with this and it's a little bit stuck
Let's make this particle diameter a little bit smaller
Well, you don't have to make it too low
Because
If the whole thing is simulated and if it's too low, the simulation will be slower
And then we're going to make the particle diameter of these smaller pieces a little bit smaller
And then we're going to simulate
That's fine
I feel like this white is a little bit too back and I'm going to change it into a yellow rice
What about the decorations in my hand we can give it and then give it a change to this white
Let's take a look at the final result
Then we start to add some decorative thread
Add some thread to the tree
The thread can be slightly larger
I set 16.3 here
I set the length of it a little bigger
Then use tweezers to make this kind of handicraft effect
I set the thickness a little bigger
Then the other side of this Christmas tree is the same
We also need to add some Christmas tree on the sleeve
There are more Christmas tree on the sleeve
OK
Let's take a look at the overall effect
Then there is our gingerbread man
We can also add some thread to him
Make his whole detail more rich
Then we give him this
Add some thread to his body
Then we give him a new one
Use another kind of thread
The length of the border here can be a little bigger
Let his color be a little bit the same as the color of our gingerbread man
Don't forget that we have another one on the other side
Then his thread can see that it didn't come out
We put this thread
This one
The reverse side is also made for him
Just change the grid face to all
There will be two sides like this
Let's take a look at the details of our gingerbread man
Look at the details of our gingerbread man
Want to know what he is
How do you know
This is theало
This is thealo
After doing it
We can exchange shoes for this model
For shoes
You can choose in the warehouse
You can also purchase on our Kinect
I downloaded this pair of shoes from the Kinect
Then you can change this model to a different posture
I feel that there is no suitable posture here
Then we can
Go to our Kinect platform
Just download one that you think is appropriate, and then apply it directly.
Then let's simulate the sound again.
Let's see the effect.
Let's also change the pattern on the bottom.
Let's see if there is any fabric that I forgot to change.
It looks a little unhappy.
This model is relatively tall.
Let's open it for him.
One of the ones we made before.
Make a matching one for him.
This is a skirt.
This is a simple white skirt.
Let's hide the sound for him first.
Then adjust the specific position.
Look at the whole thing.
Then you can.
Let's take a look at the simulation first.
Let's put this model on the surface of the shoulder first.
Reduce it.
Then adjust the position a little bit.
In order not to make him a big scale.
Unstable situation.
If you can't see, you have to adjust the position.
So this should be OK.
Then open the simulation.
Because I have a relatively low
This is a pair of socks that I made before
You can just put it in like this
This is a G-shape
Just adjust the position a little bit
But if you want to add a clothing file, you must choose to add
Otherwise, we didn't do it before
This is a hat
You can see that the hat just now
You can also adjust the position of the hat
Open this high-quality blouse to make it clearer
The hat has a little bit of a conflict with our collar
Let's freeze the hat first
We need to freeze the other panels
Or the treatment of anti-fire
The
We can give him this hat a model
Just make the collar model for him
Both of them are no longer in conflict
Because its 셋ing part is relatively small
So we can pull it out through modeling
A bit of a bit of a cut now
I'm going to make it a fire
later, I'm going to use a scarf to cover my scarf
we're going to make this version free-of-model
it's going to be frozen or re-activated
like this
when we do more models, it's going to be a bit better
the collar is very wide
later, I'm going to cover my scarf
the collar will..
because the collar is here
It will be a little shaky, so we can make a contraction of the collar first
You can just use this tail to shrink it
Then we can close the collar
It will be more convenient for us to tie the scarf later
Now we are going to do some freeze-drying and anti-ignition treatment on the collar
We are going to draw a star-shaped pattern on the collar
Now it's a bit stuck
This is the line of the collar
这个摆片位置可以稍微挪动一下 Let's move this plate a little bit
把它的颜色改一下 Let's change its color
我们把它的色纹方向给它改一下 Let's change its color direction
因为可以看到它现在是竖着的 You can see that it is vertical now
把它改成那种横着的色纹方向就可以了 Let's change it to a horizontal color direction
把它放到这个帽子上面去 Put it on the top of the hat
这样的话我们接下去一会儿模拟这样子的话我们接下去一会儿模拟 In this way, we will start to model later
我们就开始来做这个最后一步就是给它围这个围巾 We will start to make the last step, which is to give it a scarf
先把它的粒子尖就给它剪小一点 Let's make its chest a little bit smaller
然后我们把模拟打开 Then we make the model bigger
打开看一下 Open it and take a look
现在模拟速度已经很慢了 Now the simulation speed is very slow
我们就把一些没有层级关系啊 Then we put some of them that are not related to the level
然后也不会参与到模拟的这些版片给它做反击活 And then we will not participate in the simulation of these versions for it to be re-enacted
反击活的速度呢 The speed of re-enactment?
相对于模拟来说会更快一点 The speed of re-enactment will be faster compared to the simulation
这个把它做反击活 This one will be re-enacted
然后再模拟 Then re-enact
那这样子的话我们模拟速度会对比较刚刚会快很多啊 In this case, the simulation speed will be much faster compared to just now
稍微调整一下上面在帽子上的位置 Let's adjust the position on the hat a little bit
然后给它加上固定针 Then add the pin
这里我们要开始给它做一个围起来这样的操作 Here we are going to start to make a bend like this
我先给它做一个折叠的那种感觉 I'll give it a fold first
给它画一条内部线 Let's draw a line inside it
要设置一个折叠角度 To this angle of fold
这个角度 Let's draw a line inside it
这样子就可以做出这样 I can make a fold like this
我是两边这样对折的这样的一个效果 I made a fold like this
然后也给它加上固定针 Then we also add a pin
去拉动这个固定针 To pull this pin
去移动这个板片的位置 To move the position of this board
在拉的时候可以稍微的不要拉得太猛 When you pull it, you can pull it a little bit
不要拉得太猛 Don't pull it too hard
把这个雪花也给它做个反击会 I'll make a reverse of this snowflake
因为它挂到我的围巾 Because it will hang on my scarf
继续去抓我们刚刚抓住定的那根固定针 Let's continue to grab the pin we just set
去拉动这个围巾所在的这样的一个具体的位置 To pull the position of the scarf
我有点想让这个里面的这个出来一点 I kind of want this inside to come out a little bit
我们先给它定个固定针 Let's set a pin first
然后这里我们可以用这个选择网格 Then here we can use this selection grid
这个工具去把这个地方做个选择 This tool to make this place a selection
把这里的网格给它拉出来 Let's pull out the net here
可以去 We can go to
这个地方 We can go to
暂停模拟去调整它的这个围巾的这样的一个位置 Stop the model to adjust its scarf
然后可以借助我们的固定针工具 Then we can use our fixed needle tool
给它去做一个位置的一个调整 Give it a position adjustment
然后我们绕好了一边 Then we turn it around
然后我们再来拉另外一边 And then we pull it the other way
也是一样的方法都是我们去加固定针啊 It's the same way, we just add the fixed needle
然后去拉动它的位置 And then pull it to its position
就是整个围巾不要拉的太紧 Just don't pull the scarf too tight
拉太紧的话围巾会整个会变形啊 If you pull it too tight, the scarf will deform
然后我们就把这个固定针啊 And then we pull it to its position
然后通过不停的去转换它的一个视角 And then we keep changing its perspective
看它现在一个状态 To see its current state
我把刚刚那根固定针删掉 I'm going to remove the fixed needle
因为它不是很贴合这个帽子 Because it's not very close to the hat
然后围巾跟帽子稍微贴合一点 Then the scarf is a little closer to the hat
然后把这个围巾给它放下来 Then put the scarf down
另外一边也是给它绕过去 The other side is also turned around
大家可以在绕围巾 You can turn the scarf around again
在绕围巾的过程当中 In the process
可以及时的按暂停模拟 You can press the pause button in time
让这个软件记录一下那个当前的状态 So that the software can record the current state
这样后面万一冲突的话呢 If there is a conflict later
可以通过撤回回到当前的一个状态 You can go back and forth to the current state
大家在拉这个固定针的时候 You have to be careful when you pull the pin
一定要注意不要让这个固定针陷入到衣服里面去 Don't let the pin get into your clothes
及时把它拉出来 Pull it out in time
还有后面的围巾呀 And the scarf at the back
记得给它及时加这个固定针 Remember to add the pin in time
然后我们再来画一个矩形去做它那个围巾上的那个流苏 Then we will draw another square to make the silk on the scarf
做两个 Let's make two
把它做个缝合 Let's make a seam
这里我们是把它添加到侧面 Here we add it to the side
也是一样的来改一下它的这个四纹方向 It's the same, let's change its color direction
因为我们袖子反激活了 Because our sleeves are anti-activated
所以尽量不要让这个 So try not to let this panel
拉到袖子不然它就陷进去 Pull the sleeve in or it will be stuck
也可以将这个袖子给它做个冷冻 You can also make this sleeve a freezer
这样他们之间就不会有那个陷进去这种情况 So they won't have that kind of situation between them
因为冷冻的话是保留我们的层级关系的 Because the freezer keeps our layer relationship
我们把这个流苏给它应用上对应的面料 Let's apply the fabric to it
然后我们把这两个板片的粒子筋就给它降低一点 And then we're going to lower the粒子筋 of these two panels a little bit
接下来我们要把这个流苏给它做个分割 Then we're going to make a partition for this sleeve
现在我的流苏看起来它是一整片的嘛 Now my sleeve looks like it's a whole piece
直接把它做个分割 We're going to make a partition for it
先给它画这个内部线 然后直接给它做切断 We're going to draw this inner line first
然后直接给它做切断 And then we're going to cut it
这里我们就不需要再剪切粉 Let's cut it into pieces
让它切断切成一条一条的 Let's cut it into pieces
打开目镜之后就可以看到这个流苏现在这个情况了 We can see the current flow speed after we open it
然后我们把这个内部线给它删掉 Then we delete this inner line
就我们刚刚做的折叠的内部线把它删掉 We just deleted the folded inner line
可以在围巾上加一些固定针去调整这个围巾的一个具体的位置 You can add some pins on the scarf to adjust the specific position of the scarf
然后也可以通过删除一些固定针去看一下是不是有不贴合的地方 You can also delete some pins to see if there are any inconsistencies
然后我们把它整个反激活 整个激活 Let's activate it
我这里呢是那个雪花刚刚我雪花是把反激活掉了 I'm here with the snowflake. Just now my snowflake has been reactivated.
把我们的雪花给它激活不然它跟流苏那个地方会有一点模拟的话可能会有一点冲突啊 Let's activate our snowflake for it. Otherwise, it will have a little conflict with the flow speed.
要先把这个地方给它模拟好我们才能把我们才能把这个地方给它模拟好 我们才能把这个地方给它模拟好
整件给它做激活 Activate the whole thing for it.
然后我们把那个我们的圣诞树背景给它加进来 Then we add the background of our Christmas tree to it.
让我的圣诞树有点大一下 让它进来稍微慢了一点 Then my Christmas tree is a little big and now it's a little bit slower to come in.
把这个 Let's put this
梨花的位置稍微挪一下 Put it in the position of the peony a little bit.
给它看一下渲染 Okay, let's see the rendering.
因为我整个场景比较大 I made the whole scene bigger.
我渲染一下 Let me render it.
稍微有点慢 It's a little slow.
好 出来了 Okay, it's out.
这样子呢就是我们整个的一个这样子呢就是我们整个的一个 So this is our whole
毛衣的一个制作 就是我们的圣诞的一个风味的一个制作 a work of a sweater, a work of a Christmas phoenix.
大家如果有问题的话呢可以在评论里面跟我说 If you have any questions, you can tell me in the comments.
最后我们是做成了这样子一个效果 So this is the final result.
祝大家元旦快乐,祝大家元旦快乐,我们这次的直播到这里就结束啦。